For more text formatting options,
cue-2
click the
cue-3
three dots more icons in the toolbar.
cue-4
You can underline and strikethrough text
cue-5
and make subscripts and superscripts.
cue-6
Remember to avoid overusing underlined
text,
cue-7
as it can be confused with links.
cue-8
To create lists, headings, and block
quotes,
cue-9
click the
cue-10
format dropdown and select your desired
format.
cue-11
The list and heading formats open
additional toolbar options when selected.
cue-12
Use a list format for bulleted or numbered
items.
cue-13
You can use these to additionally adjust
your list and headings.
cue-14
For accessibility, remember to use a
heading format for section headers
cue-15
and avoid using simply bold or italicized
text.
cue-16
At the end of paragraph toolbar are the
undo and redo buttons,
cue-17
which allow you to undo and redo changes
that you make within this paragraph block.